O blessed Rome!
O blessed Rome, most noble.
O blessed Rome, blessed Rome, most noble Rome.
You are the seat of Peter, who takes the place of Christ,
You are the seat of Peter, who is an apostle of peace.
Pontiff, we will all be with you,
Pontiff, you are the teacher who confirms your brothers,
Pontiff, our strength and foundation,
Fisher of men, shepherd of the flock, linking heaven and earth.
Peter, you are the Vicar of Christ on the earth,
Amidst the waves, you are a beacon, and the truth.
You are the love of Christ, you are the guardian of unity,
Prompt defender of liberty; authority in you.
Peter, you are the Vicar of Christ on the earth,
Amidst the waves, you are a beacon, and the truth.
You are the love of Christ, you are the guardian of unity,
Watchful defender of liberty; in You is the authority.